webpageing.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy

### 1\. What information does Webpageing.com collect?

At different times, Webpageing.com may collect several types of information about you. Except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy, we do not provide this information to third parties, except in aggregate form.

First, we or our partners or advertisers may use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer - but not you - to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. You can turn the cookies feature off by using your browser's preference options, but if you do so you may not be able to utilize some services properly.

Second, we keep track of your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our site. Your IP address is a number that identifies a computer which accesses the Internet. This address is used to gather broad demographic information about you, such as your Internet service provider and the geographic location of your IP address. Webpageing.com may also collect aggregate information on how our users are utilizing the site. This might include information regarding traffic patterns through the site and search queries.

Third, we log browser types, access times, URLs from which visitors came to our site and URLs viewed by visitors while on our site. Again, Webpageing.com uses this information on an aggregate basis, in this case making sure we can support overall visitor traffic and service performance.

Fourth, at specific times we may ask you to provide us with personal information to enable you to register for a service or to enter a sweepstakes. You may also provide personal information if you write us feedback email. This information may include but is not limited to your name and email address. You may always choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service, offer you personalized content, or respond to your feedback.

Fifth, our service partners may collect information on our behalf about our users' visiting behaviors in several ways, including through the use of cookies or pixel tags. We use these service partners to understand what is popular and useful for visitors. Our service partners are contractually prohibited from disclosing this information to any third party.

### 2\. What organization is collecting the information?

Webpageing.com usually collects the requested information. However, Webpageing.com has chosen select partners to provide certain services. To use certain services on the site, it may be necessary to enter information that then goes to our partner and is not kept by Webpageing.com. The areas of our site in which partners are collecting information may be cobranded with our partners' logos. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data collection practices of one of our content partners, please contact that partner directly.

### 3\. What does Webpageing.com do with the data it collects?

Whenever Webpageing.com collects data, the data is intended to tailor or improve the experience of visitors to our site. From the data collected we can customize content and advertising based on the user's preferences. We may use information from cookies to differentiate between unique users, personalize the site for each unique user, to control the frequency of individual advertisements directed to individual computers, and other purposes. In all cases, personally identifiable information is not shared with our advertisers, except as otherwise stated in this privacy policy.

We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. It's the way we can make sure our service is consistently available to you.

If you register for a service or to enter a sweepstakes, we may use the information we collect to provide the service to you or send communications regarding the sweepstakes. We may also send a newsletter by email to our users who opt to receive such emails. It is our policy to send these emails only to users who give us permission to do so. In every such email, we will also have instructions on how to unsubscribe to avoid receiving any future emails from us. Webpageing.com also may contact you by email to respond to feedback you have submitted.

### 4\. With whom does Webpageing.com share data?

Webpageing.com may disclose your personal information to our business partners to provide you with the services you have requested, or to companies that offer a cobranded version of our site. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data-collection practices of one of our business partners, please contact that partner directly. Webpageing.com does not have control over and is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of our business partners. Webpageing.com may also disclose your personal information to other members of the Webpageing.com family of businesses.

We also may disclose your personal information (including without limitation IP addresses) to a third party if the law or legal process requires it, to protect the rights or property of Webpageing.com or others, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We may disclose certain non-personally identifiable information about you to advertisers or other third parties to present you with targeted advertisements. We may share aggregate demographic information with our advertisers or information collection companies, but will not reveal any personally identifiable information in these instances.
